const grade5data=[
    {
        question:"April",
        choices:["8月","9月","4月","5月"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"art",
        choices:["肖像","美術","絵画","映画"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"bag",
        choices:["鞄","虫","後ろ","紐"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"breakfast",
        choices:["早朝","朝食","朝会","起床"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"brother",
        choices:["友達","親子","家族","兄弟"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"call back",
        choices:["呼ぶ","電話をかけ直す","叫ぶ","電話をする"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"hold on",
        choices:["かかえる","手を挙げる","待つ","落ち着く"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"look for",
        choices:["探す","見つける","見つめる","睨む"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"get to",
        choices:["出発する","得る","到着する","受け取る"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"do homework",
        choices:["手伝いをする","掃除をする","宿題をする","洗濯する"],
        answer:2
    }
]

export default grade5data;